Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  - Ian and Sylvia concert, November 12, 1966, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR316)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Ian and Sylvia with David Rae, lead guitar. Performing at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Performed and recorded November 12, 1966. For song list see Appendix A. Copy from 7-inch reels (SR155-SR157).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, March 4, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR158)
    Reel 1 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Dave Van Ronk. Performing at Sprague Hall, Yale University. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, March 4, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR159)
    Reel 2 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Dave Van Ronk. Performing at Sprague Hall, Yale University. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, March 4, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR160)
    Reel 3 of 3. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Dave Van Ronk. Performing at Sprague Hall, Yale University. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Dave Van Ronk concert, March 4, 1967, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR313)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Dave Van Ronk performing at Sprague Hall, Yale University. Copy from 7-inch reels.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 14, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR161)
    Reel 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Billy Hamilton and the Ohio River Boys, Lew Sellinger, Bob Mehrer, Roy Berkeley, String Temperance String Band (Allan Block, Ralph Lee Smith, Andy May, and Eric Nagler), and Mary Jo Olsen. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 14, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR162)
    Reel 2 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Mary Jo Olsen, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Ana Perez, John Burke and Andy May, Roger Sprung with Jack Lund, Dave Kiphuth and Arnie Feldman, and Ed Freeman. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 14, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR163)
    Reel 3 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Ed Freeman, High Tension Tim and the Live Wires (Tim Woodbridge, Arnie Feldman, Dick Blaustein, John Burke, Rosemary Blaustein), Jim Bennett, Stephen Moitozo, and Pete Peterson. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, May 14, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR164)
    Reel 4 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Karl Ecklund, Shirley Keller, Shire Folk, and Ana Perez. For song list see Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR165)
    Reel 1 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Pete Peterson, the Twighlights (Shirley Keller and Lionel Kilberg), Roy Berkeley, Golden Age Retrievers (Tim Woodbridge, Pete Peterson, Dick Menn, and John Burke), Caroline Paton, Bill Hamilton and the Ohio River Valley Boys, and Bart Hobson.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR166)
    Reel 2 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bart Hobson, Harry and Jeannie West with Winnie Winston, Al Silverman, Art Rosenbaum, Allan Block, and Ralph Lee Smith, Linda Hughes, Karl Ecklund, and Bob Stuart, Arnie Feldman, Tom Hayes, and Ralph Lee Smith, Guy MacKenzie, Pete Wernick, Andy May, Steve Arkin, and Tim Woodbridge, Artie Rose, and Ken Kosek.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR167)
    Reel 3 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Winnie Winston, Artie Rose, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Pete Colby, the Cedar Bog Boys (Ray Prinz, Tim Woodbridge, Jack Lund, Dave Kiputh, Ken Kosek), Bill Burke, Ken Kosek and Andy May, Four Jovial Brothers (Cliff Haslam), and Steve Arkin.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR168)
    Reel 4 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Steve Arkin, Pigment (Marty Brennan, Jim Buchanan, Steve Winchell), Maxine O'Bacmority and Lionel Kilberg. Also includes "old timey recordings before and after Saturday night hoot (including Allan Block, Dave Howard, Pete Peterson, Jack Lund, John Burke, Sandy Kaplan, Ralph Lee Smith, Lionel Kilberg, and Art Rosenbaum)."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR169)
    Reel 5 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert. "More Old Timey Miscellany recorded around and about."
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR170)
    Indian Folk Festival concert and jam session featuring Roger Sprung, Arnie Feldman, Allan Block, John Burke, Tim Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, Andy May, and John Biltchik.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, November 22, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR171)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Gordon Bok concert at Woolsey Hall, Yale University.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, November 22, 1969, I sound cassette (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR317)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Gordon Bok concert at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Copy from 7-inch reels.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR172)
    Reel 1 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Lionel Kilberg, Jack Lund, Roy Berkeley, Ed Tipton, Pete Peterson, Star Spangled String Band, and Shirley Keller.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR173)
    Reel 2 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Shirley Keller, Ohio River Boys, Pete Colby, Andy Leader, Roy Berkeley and Bob Stewart, Rick and Lorraine Lee, and Pete Wernick.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR174)
    Reel 3 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Pete Wernick, Tim Woodbridge, John Burke, R.L. Smith, Pete Peterson, Jack Bartman, Gordon Bok, Harry and Jeannie West, and Tom Paley.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR175)
    Reel 4 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Cliff Haslam, Jim McGrath, Jack Parnelli, Friday evening singing in game room, Bart Hobson, Margaret MacArthur, Gordon Bok, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR176)
    Reel 5 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival. Saturday afternoon music featuring Jim McGrath, Cliff Haslam, Gordon Bok, Andy Leader, Bob Stewart, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR177)
    Reel 6 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival. Sunday morning music featuring Jack Bertman, John Smolow, Bart Hobson, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR178)
    Reel 7 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival. Sunday morning music featuring Jack Bertman and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, August 10, 1969, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR179)
    1969 field recordings at Fox Hollow by Arnie Feldman and Peter Colby. Song list in Appendix A.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR181)
    Reel 1 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring John Coffey, Shirley Keller, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Allan Block and Pete Peterson, Ken Kosek and Andy May, Roy Berkeley, John Roberts and Tony Barrand, Pete Colby and Mary Faith Rhoads, Ed Lipton, John Coffey, Pete Colby and Tim Woodbridge, Betsy Rutherford, Gordon Bok, and Harry and Jeanie West.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR182)
    Reel 2 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Pete Peterson, Dallas Cline, Golden Nectar Good Time Band, Cliff Haslam, Al Schwartz, Margaret MacArthur, Harry Tuft, Ed Trickett, Bill Burke, Sara Grey, Barry O’Neill, Kenny Kosek, Andy May, Artie Rose, and Dave Kiphuth.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR183)
    Reel 3 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Nick Appolonio, Kenny Kosek, Victor Levine, Nick Felder, Jerry LaSala, as well as Friday evening miscellany and Sunday afternoon medley.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR184)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Pete Peterson, Allan Block, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 18, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR180)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Gordon Bok, Sara Grey (with Ed Trickett and Harry Tuft) concert, Sprague Hall, Yale University.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, April 18, 1970, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR343)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Gordon Bok and Sara Grey (with Ed Trickett and Harry Tuft) at Woolsey Hall, Yale University. Copy from 7-inch reel (SR180).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR185)
    Reel 1 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR186)
    Reel 2 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR187)
    Reel 3 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, and Friday evening singing.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR188)
    Reel 1 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Saturday evening concert featuring the Greater New England Blap Band, Maggi Peirce, Dave Kiphuth and Mike Rivers, Betsy Rutherford and John Coffey, Fayette Street Ragtime Band, Jay Ungar and Jon Wilcox, and the Golden Age Retrievers.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR189)
    Reel 2 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Saturday evening concert featuring Jeff Warner, Gail Fratar Benham and Kathy Spencer, Ted Levin and Gail Benham, Jay Ungar or Jeff Warner (?), Sandy Davis and Bill Smith, George and Vaughn Ward, David Jones, The Old Clawgrass Boys, Estelle Wade, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR190)
    Reel 3 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday afternoon concert featuring the MacArthurs and friends, Allan Block and friends, Roy Berkeley, Mike Rivers, the New Battleship Potemkin String Ensemble, and Shirley Keller and Charlie Wright.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR191)
    Reel 4 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday afternoon and Sunday night concerts featuring the Lower Fayette St. Chowder and Marching Society Sacred Harp Singing Convention and Friends, Jon Wilcox, Rick and Lorraine Lee with Bill Burke (Cabin Fever), Barbara Carns, Gordon Bok, Karl and Shirley Eklund, and Helen Schneyer.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR192)
    Reel 5 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday night concert featuring Helen Schneyer (continued), Cliff Haslam, Jonathan Eberhart, Neal MacMillan and Joanie Bronfman, Kay Covington, Don Duncan, Penny McHutchinson and Jerry Weene, Jerry Weene and Ted Levin.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR193)
    Reel 6 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday night concert featuring the Bill Garbus and Dave Spilkia Old Timey Orchestra, Gordon Bok and Annie Muir, Dave Kaynor, Art Bryan, Martin Grosswendt, and Andy Wallace.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR194)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR195)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR196)
    Reel 3 of 3. Concert dub. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR011)
    Cassette 1 of 10. Concert featuring Blarp Band, David Jones, Sedalia City String Band, Roy Berkeley, Common Ground, and April Limber.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR012)
    Cassette 2 of 10. Concert featuring Mudsuckers, Debby McClatchy, Tim and Jerry, Pete and Rebecca, and Block Family.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR013)
    Cassette 3 of 10. Concert featuring Rory Block, Saletans, and Paul Cadwell.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR014)
    Cassette 4 of 10. Concert featuring Neil Rossi, Helen Schneyer, and the Shimbergs.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR015)
    Cassette 5 of 10. Concert featuring the Lees, Johnathan Eberhart, New Harmony Sisterhood, Smuckler Family, and Mike Holmes.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR016)
    Concert featuring Mike Holmes, Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMillan, and Cliff Haslam.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR017)
    Cassette 6 of 10. Concert featuring Cliff Haslam and Hank Schwartz Workman, Mark Gilsten, Charlie Wright, Shirley Keller, and Marshall Dodge.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR018)
    Cassette 7 of 10. Concert featuring Marshall Dodge and Margaret MacArthur.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR019)
    Cassette 8 of 10.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR020)
    Cassette 9 of 10. Concert featuring Paul Cadwell, Liz and Pat Eckert, John Cowles, Mark Surgies, and Dwayne Thorpe.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1974, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR021)
    Cassette 10 of 10. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday concert featuring Kathy Spencer and a jam session.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR022)
    Cassette 1 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Blar Band, Maggi Peirce, Sedalia String Band, Roy Berkeley, Maxine Weiner, Helen Schneyer, Ken Segal and Rebecca Sundry, Gilston's Golden Gaida with Daniel Jones, Lisa Neustadt and friends.'
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR023)
    Cassette 2 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Tony and Irene Saleton, Nitpickers, May Bryan, PCCB, Rick and Lorraine Lee, and Mike Holmes.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR024)
    Cassette 3 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Mike Holmes, Barbara Carns, Captain American and the Bluegrass Patriots, Debbie McClatchy, Joanie Bronfman and Neil MacMillan, and Bruce Hutton.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR025)
    Cassette 4 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bruce Hutton, Dwayne Thorpe, David Jones, Cliff Haslam, Indian Chief Tans, Ken Feit, and Rick Schoenberg.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR026)
    Cassette 5 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Rick Schoenberg, George Wilson and Debbie Saperstone, Jonathan Eberhart, Bob Zantz, Estelle Wade, Eileen Derry and Gabi Kundert, Lisa Preston, Hank Schwartz, Ebenezer, Kathy Torrey, and Lani and Maria and friends.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR027)
    Cassette 1 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bob Geer and friends, Neil Rossi, Overcast Trio, Ted Strater, Bob Stuart, Dave Olive, Evan Leonard, and Tom Gibney.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR028)
    Cassette 7 of 7. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Tom Gibney, Jay Smith, Kathy Spencer and friends, George and Vaughn Ward, Joel and Kathy Shimberg, Art, Laurie, April, Pete, Deanna, and Pierre, and The Promenade Deck Orchestra.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR212)
    Reel 1 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Blap Band, Maggi Peirce, Maxine Weiner, Sedalia String Band, Roy Berkeley, Helen Schneyer and Jonathan Eberhart, Ken Segal, Rebecca Saunders, Mark Gilston with Dave Jones, and Lisa Neustadt.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR197)
    Reel 2 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Lisa Neustadt, Tony and Irene Saletan, Nitpickers, Mary Bryan, Paul Cadwell, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Mike Holmes with Rick and Lorraine Lee and Reed Martin, and Maggi Peirce.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR198)
    Reel 3 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Barbara Carns (with Jonathan Eberhart) Captain America and the Bluegrass Patriots, Debbie McClatchy, Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMillan, the Goodfolk (Joe and Lisa Cenis with David Kaynor), Bruce Hutton, and Dwayne Thorpe.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR199)
    Reel 4 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Dwayne Thorpe, David Jones, Cliff Haslam, Indian Chieftans (Ted Levin and friends), Ken Feit with Art Bryan, Rick Schoenberg, George Wilson and Debby Saperstone, Jonathan Eberhardt, Bob Gear and Ted Strader, and Bob Zentz.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR200)
    Reel 5 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bob Zentz, Estelle Wade, Eileen Derry, Lisa Preston, Gabi Kundert, Hank Schwartz, Ebenezer (Allan Block, George Wilson, Nancy McDowell), Kathy Torrey, Lannie Liggeria, Rose Zak and Marcia Deihl, Robert Gear, and Jonathan Eberhart.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR201)
    Reel 6 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Neil Rossi, Overcast Trio (Colin Quigley, Jim Miller, Jeff Woodring), Ted Strader and Jonathan Eberhart, Bob Stuart, Dave Olive, Evan Leonard and the Banjo Barracudas, and Tom Gibney.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR202)
    Reel 1 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival Saturday evening concert featuring the Secular Harp, Debby McClatchy, Roy Berkeley with Tim Woodbridge, Bob Stuart and Dave Kiphuth, Lisa Neustadt, Pam Swing (Sandy Davis, Bill Smith, Sara Gregory, Dinty Child), Cliff Haslam, Mark Gilston, and Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMillan.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR204)
    Reel 2 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Neil and Joni, Helen Schneyer with daughter and Jonathan Eberhart, David Jones, Barbara Carns Cadwell, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Bob Franke, and Bob Zentz.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR205)
    Reel 3 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival Saturday night and Sunday concerts featuring Delaware Watergap String Band, Maggi Peirce, Bruce Hutton, Mark Cushing and Alotta Fitzgerald, Pipers, Tom Gibney, Archie Fisher, Captain America and the Bluegrass Patriots, Lisa Null with Kathy Westra, and Dave Olive.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR206)
    Reel 4 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday concert featuring Dave Olive, Priscilla Herdman, Margaret MacArthur, Bill Chute with Lisa Null, Neil Rossi, Dildines, Jay Smith, Joan Sprung, Arthur E. Smith Prairie Ramblers, and Ann and Lani Herrmann.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR207)
    Reel 5 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Ann and Lani Herrmann, Don Duncan, Dave Keynor, Joan Pelton, George Ward, Wendy Grossman, Caroline Paton, Ann Muir, Joan Sprung, Leslie Shatuel, and the Sedalia String Band.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR029)
    Cassette 1 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Secular Harp Singers, Debby McClatchy, Roy Berkeley, Bob Stuart, Lisa Neustadt, Common Ground, Cliff Haslam, and Mark Gilston.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR030)
    Cassette 2 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Helen Schneyer, David Jones, Jonathan Eberhart, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Bob Franke, and Bob Zentz.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR031)
    Cassette 3 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bob Zentz, Maggi Peirce, Bruce Hutton, and Mark Cushing and Alotta Fitzgerald.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR032)
    Cassette 4 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Highland Pipers, Tom Gibnoy, Archie Fisher, Captain America and the Bluegrass Patriots. Lisa Null, Dave Olive, Priscilla Herdman, Margaret McArthur.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR033)
    Cassette 5 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bill Shute with Lisa Null, Neil Rossi, Jay Smith, Joan Sprung, AES Prairie Ramblers, Don Duncan, Dave Kaynor, and Joan Pelton.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1976, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR034)
    Cassette 6 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring George Ward, Wendy Grossman, Caroline Paton, Ann Muir, Leslie Shotwell, and Sedalia City S.B.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR035)
    Cassette 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring George Balderosa, Joan Sprung and Lani Herrmann, Mark Surgies, Roy Berkeley and Woodbridge, Neal MacMillan and Joanie Bronfman, Abigail Stewart and Dave Sedalia, David Jones, and Jonathan Eberhart.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR036)
    Cassette 2 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jonathan Eberhart, Ajemian, Randy Miller and Shirley Keller, Matty Levine and Bruce Hutton, Ralph Lee Smith, Maggi Peirce, Lisa Neustadt, and Lani and Ann.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR037)